denso-ten.com 2019-07-11

# Privacy Policy | DENSO TEN

DENSO TEN Limited and the DENSO TEN Group (hereinafter referred to as "TEN Group") strongly recognize that the protection of personal information (customer names, addresses, e-mail addresses and any other information that can be used to identify an individual) is our corporate social responsibility, and promise to guard and respect customers' personal information according to the policy outlined below.

## I. Handling of Personal Information

TEN Group has established regulations concerning the handling of personal information. In addition to ensuring that all employees who handle personal information are thoroughly aware of these regulations, we have designated an employee in charge of handling personal information in each department, and deal with said information appropriately at all times.  
In addition, we implement appropriate security measures to prevent illicit access to personal information as well as loss, falsification, leakage or other misuses.

## II. Acquisition of Personal Information

When acquiring personal information from customers, TEN Group clearly states the purposes for which it will be used, and acquires only such information as is necessary, using fair and legitimate methods.

## III. Use of Personal Information

TEN Group uses personal information only within the range of the purposes clearly stated to customers when the information was acquired. When necessary for said purposes, the information may be provided to outside contractors. At such times, contractors are required by written agreements, etc., to handle information in an appropriate manner.

## IV. Disclosure and Entrusting of Information to Third Parties

TEN Group does not disclose or entrust customers' personal information to third parties without the consent of the customer. However, exceptions may be made when required by law, or in response to rulings or directives from legal authorities.  
TEN Group may use personal information jointly with other Group companies when required by the purposes of use described in section 3.

## V. Requests for Disclosure, etc.

For inquiries related to the disclosure, correction, deletion, etc., of personal information held by TEN Group, please contact us at [webmaster@tm.ten.fujitsu.com.](mailto:webmaster@tm.ten.fujitsu.com.) We will respond with all sincerity after confirming the identity of the inquiring party.

## VI. Compliance with Laws and Regulations

TEN Group complies with the Personal Information Protection Law and all related regulations, making all necessary improvements to our handling of personal information.
